b1.org 2018-11-06

# B1 Free Archiver

### Privacy Policy

B1 Free Archiver, Catalina Group Ltd's product, ("B1 Free Archiver") faithfully treats your personal info and privacy. Please look through the following to learn more about B1 Free Archiver's Privacy Policy ("Policy"). This Policy deals with the way how B1 Free Archiver receives and uses information in connection with our website and software provided on the b1.org website (hereinafter referred to as the as "Site").

### Collection and Use of Information

You have to be aware about the fact that B1 Free Archiver does not knowingly collect any personal data that can identify a user, such as e-mail, name, login names, telephone numbers, address and passwords or any other self-identifying information (hereinafter referred to as the "Personal Information"). B1 Free Archiver shall take all reasonable measures to protect users' personal data from unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction. B1 Free Archiver reserves the right to use cookies on the Site. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to a hard drive for records management. Cookies simplify the web-surfing process by saving parameters and browsing settings while you are at B1 Free Archiver's Site. Cookies may be used to: analyze the process of the Site usage, improve and customize the Site's content and layout as well as for other purposes of customer service. B1 Free Archiver's use of cookies is by no means aimed at gathering any Personal Information.

B1 Free Archiver may automatically receive and save some non-personally identifiable information at its server, such as logs from the user's browser, including IP-address, type of browser, internet service provider (ISP), cookie, and a webpage that is being visited. B1 Free Archiver collects non-personally identifiable information only for general purposes, including but not limited to tracking user movements, administering the site, analyzing trends, conducting research and providing anonymous reporting to external and internal clients. 

### Sharing and Disclosure of Information

B1 Free Archiver does not sell, rent, or share any personally identifiable information about the user to the third-parties. B1 Free Archiver reserves the right to disclose your Personal Information if B1 Free Archiver believes such action is necessary to: 

  * Stay in compliance with the law or legal process served at B1 Free Archiver
  * Protect the rights or property of B1 Free Archiver (including the enforcement of our agreements) 
  * Act in urgent situations to protect the personal safety of users of B1 Free Archiver services. 

Epom Ltd. may collect data related to the use of B1 File Manager and Archiver other apps and user's device, that may include (a combination of) Personal Data elements, such as geographical location, network performance, and other permission-based information. 

Data is collected and treated anonymously and shared with other partners so that users can receive more effective ads in B1 File Manager and Archiver applications. For more details please refer to Epom's [Privacy Policy](https://apps.epom.com/privacy-policy). 

### Spyware and Adware

We oppose spyware and adware. Spyware is software installed on your computer without your consent or control. It can record and transmit your Internet activity and other personal information or change your computer's security settings. Adware is spyware that sends you unwanted pop-ups or spam. B1 Free Archiver by no means uses these unwanted and harmful technologies.

### Children's Privacy

Keeping safe the privacy of very young people is especially important for us. We operate our website in accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). We never collect or keep any information at our website from those who we know are under 13. Any part of our website is not aimed at attracting anyone under 13\. Visitors younger than 13 years old are not allowed to use the B1 Free Archiver website and software and must LEAVE the current web site immediately.

### Explicit Content

You have to be aware that by using the Service, you can face the content that may imply indecent, offensive, or objectionable info that may or may not be identified as being an explicit language. Notwithstanding that, you agree to use the Site or the Application at your sole risk. You also agree that B1 Free Archiver shall have no liability to you for content that may seem offensive, indecent, or objectionable. B1 Free Archiver shall have no liability to you for any materials that may be accessible in connection with the Site or the Application that you might find offensive.

### Security

B1 Free Archiver takes reasonable precaution to protect Personal Information from excessive use, data dump and unauthorized access. Although B1 Free Archiver cannot guarantee that Personal Information will not be subject to unauthorized access due to customer's fault. B1 Free Archiver has procedural, electronic, and physical safeguards to protect the Personal Information. Personal Information is protected by secured networks and access is limited to a few authorized employees. 

### Third Party Links and Co-Brand Relationships

In an attempt to provide increased value to our visitors, we may choose various third party web sites or services to link to, and frame within, the Sites or Services. We also participate in co-branding and other relationships to offer e-commerce and other services and features to our users. However, even if the third party is affiliated with us, we have no control over these linked sites, each of which has separate privacy and data collection practices independent of us. Data collected by our co-brand partners or third party web sites (even if offered on or through our site) may not be received by us. As such, we have no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions, and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any such web sites. These linked sites are only for your convenience and you therefore access them at your own risk.

### Changes to Policy

B1 Free Archiver reserves the right to revise this Policy from time to time. B1 Free Archiver will post the revised Policy on its Site, so that users can constantly be aware of what kind of information B1 Free Archiver collects, in what way the information is used and according to what circumstances such information may be disclosed.

### Change or Removal of Information

In case a user decides to change or remove his/her e-mail address or other personal information, contact us at [support@b1.org](mailto:support@b1.org) with the request.

### Contact Information

Please send all questions concerning the Policy via e-mail to: [support@b1.org](mailto:support@b1.org) as well.

Date of last revision October 31, 2013   
Copyright © 2015, Catalina Group Ltd. All rights reserved.
